Another great Restorative for releasing back tension is placing your legs up the wall.
And you could do this with or without support, depends how high you want to lift your pelvis up.
I place a chair here instead of; I don't have a wall nearby.
So what you'll do is you'll scoot your bolster down, towards the wall.
You have your single folded blanket in the back.
With the wall it's a little bit easier to do this, but what you'll do is you bring your behind up, so you probably want to scoot the bolster even closer.
Then slowly scoot, if the wall was right here, so I'm going to scoot my wall closer, but you'll put your legs to the side and press your toes into the wall and then let yourself, legs go up the wall.
Now my blanket, I need to scoot down, make sure it's nice and flat, any kinks within the blankets will make it quite uncomfortable.
And then slowly bring your legs up the wall.
And with an actual wall here, you'll have support on your behind, all the way up your legs.
You can let your legs rest slightly.
This helps get circulation, the blood flowing down from the feet.
If you spend a lot of time on your feet standing, anything like this, this is an excellent posture for relieving leg tension, helping get the blood out if you've got varicose veins problem and things like that, this also helps.
Set your timer, grab your eye pillow and just rest your hand on your stomach.
And that's Legs Up The Wall Pose.